const STORE = [
    {
        question: 'WHEN SPEAKING ABOUT RUNNING FORM, THE LEG THAT IS CURRENTLY BEHIND YOUR CENTER OF MASS IS REFERRED TO AS WHAT?',
        answers: [
            "LEAD LEG",
            "RIGHT LEG",
            "BEHIND LEG",
            "TRAIL LEG"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "TRAIL LEG"
    },
    {
        question: 'IN TRACK & FIELD, HOW MANY PEOPLE ARE ON A RELAY TEAM?',
        answers: [
            "5",
            "10",
            "4",
            "AMOUNT VARIES"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "4"
    },
    {
        question: 'IN A PRE-RUN STRETCH ROUTINE, WHICH TYPE OF STRETCHING EXERCISES ARE MOST HIGHLY RECOMMENDED?',
        answers: [
            "DYNAMIC",
            "STATIC",
            "NO STRETCHING",
            "TYPES DO NOT VARY"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "DYNAMIC"
    },
    {
        question: 'WHEN ANALYZING THE EFFICIENCY OF RUNNING FORM, WHICH MEASUREMENT IS THE MOST IMPORTANT?',
        answers: [
            "STRIDE LENGTH",
            "GROUND FORCE",
            "CORE POSITIONING",
            "ALL THREE"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "ALL THREE"
    },
    {
        question: 'WHICH TYPE OF NUTRIENT IS RECOMMENDED FOR PROPER POST-WORKOUT NUTRITION?',
        answers: [
            "CALCIUM",
            "PROTEIN",
            "GLUCOSE",
            "ALL THREE"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "ALL THREE"
    },
    {
        question: 'WHAT IS THE MOST EFFICIENT FUEL SOURCE TO BURN DURING A RUN?',
        answers: [
            "CARBOHYDRATES",
            "FATS",
            "PROTEIN",
            "CAKE"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "FATS"
    },
    {
        question: 'WHICH NUTRIENT INCREASES THE AMOUNT OF OXYGEN THAT INDIVIDUAL RED BLOOD CELLS ARE ABLE TO CARRY?',
        answers: [
            "CARBOHYDRATES",
            "IRON",
            "POTASSIUM",
            "PROTEIN"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "CARBOHYDRATES"
    },
    {
        question: 'WHO CURRENTLY(AS OF AUGUST, 2019) HOLDS THE OFFICIAL(AND UNOFFICIAL) WORLD RECORD FOR THE MARATHON DISTANCE?',
        answers: [
            "WILSON KIPSANG",
            "MOHAMMED FARAH",
            "ELIUD KIPCHOGE",
            "GALEN RUPP"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "ELIUD KIPCHOGE"
    },
    {
        question: 'LIVING AT WHICH ALTITUDE IS MOST EFFECTIVE FOR LONG DISTANCE TRAINING?',
        answers: [
            "LOW",
            "SEA-LEVEL",
            "HIGH",
            "DOES NOT MATTER"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "HIGH"
    },
    {
        question: 'WHO IS THE MOST DOMINANT TRACK & FIELD SPRINTER OF ALL TIME?',
        answers: [
            "MICHAEL JOHNSON",
            "USAIN BOLT",
            "CARL LEWIS",
            "TOO CLOSE TO CALL"
        ],
        correctAnswer: "USAIN BOLT"
    }
]